growing your email list is one of the
most important things that you can do if
you are a coach or course creator online
to grow your business and the reason why
is that it's more than just having a
contact list or an audience it's the
single most determining factor to your
ability to be successful financially in
your
business when you grow your email list
it gives you an opportunity to connect
with these people and be able to get
more sales in my business the the direct
there's a direct correlation between me
getting new people on my email list and
the amount of sales that I get in my
business when I'm not adding new people
in my email list I see a drop in sales
when I start adding more people to the
list there is an increase in sales and
this goes across the board in every
single business that we have built as
far as that goes and
so the best ways to do so to get people
on your email list is social media and
paid advertising those are those are the
numberb
main ways if you're just trying to get
people to become a client of yours who
are already on your list you're
marketing the same people who are
already following you organically on
social media and not getting new people
that have never met you before in the
door with you see most coaches and
mentors nobody knows necessarily who you
are when you're coming out the gate and
so if we're trying to get people to buy
from us when they don't know who we are
and we're and we're trying to build
trust with them it becomes very
difficult to get them to say Okay I want
to purchase with you unless they have
this buying temperature that is
increased anytime that somebody's going
to be buying your coaching program they
have a belief and a trust that's going
to deliver a transformation and a result
to them and there's a 21-day window from
the time that somebody joins your email
list to when they're most likely to buy
from you after that 21-day window you
have to Loop them back around into
another offer to increase that level of
train trust if they fizzled out and so
there's going to be a group of people in
there not everybody's going to buy from
you but they're going to buil be built
in in with trust they're going to buy
from you in that 21-day period those
that drop off we Loop them back around
to a new offer simply put the way that
we grow our email list is we deliver
value to people some kind of quick win
that people can get the there's a couple
of ways that I grow my email list and
I'm going to show you those right now um
that we've done just in the last couple
of months in my
business and is here's an offer right
here um where I created it's like a it's
like
a 30 38 minute instant class that people
get access to they they give me their
name and email address they get instant
access to this class all about Facebook
ads and artificial intelligence this is
actually one of my best performing
campaigns another one that I did right
here this one did really good a ton of
leads to grow my email list I actually
got a lot of clients off of this one as
well 42 minutes long uh training all
about starting your own sixf figure
online course or coaching business right
here okay now we did one more
recently um that was a 3-day intensive
this is what a three-day intensive is
right
here is and you know forgive me at the
time of this recording it seems like our
internet connection is just a little bit
slower than we're used to uh build and
grow your sixf figure group coaching
membership January 15th through 17th so
again now this has paid this cost $7 I
was able to Market this the people who
are already on my email list but we
actually got a lot of brand new people
who signed up for it because it was low
cost another offer to gr our email us
are these chat gbt prompts things like
that and so what I look at is anything
that solves a problem for somebody that
gets them something that they desire
that's what I use to grow my email list
and then in that that is where I have
email sequences that come after that
limited time offers I have exclusive
offers with bonuses for people to become
clients and when we do this it
translates somebody from just joining
your list to becoming a client of yours
now even if somebody is already on your
email list we still need to Loop them
back through some kind of a buying
experience and here's why because people
get distracted they're water heat breaks
down they will prioritize that over
hiring you any day of the week and so
what we have to do is we have to realize
that like if somebody is not becoming a
client of yours it's probably because
there's other stuff in their life that's
more important that's pulling their
attention no matter how good your offer
is has nothing to do with how your offer
being bad it has everything to do with
the fact that there's not a a connection
in the last 21 days that has been made
with somebody to persuade them to be to
buy from you and become your CL client
okay so that's what we look at and
that's what we create and we create
offers to grow our email list and so
when it comes to creating offers to
Growing our email list we got to look at
what is the thing that somebody desires
the most what is the deepest desire
that's going to solve the problem for
them to move them away from the pain
that they have we want to move people
away from Pain we're not leading with
pain we're moving them into their
desires we're not triggering the pain to
the point that they feel the pain we're
getting them to realize oh I don't want
this no more I actually want something
much better much more
satisfying and that's exactly what we
help our clients with in my wealthy
coach Academy program formerly known as
our client growth accelerator we've now
renamed it to the wealthy coach Academy
program I'd love to see you in there
with us I work with people every single
week I come alongside them and I show
them everything from their ads to their
sales copy their landing pages to
everything that you say and how to say
it to to successfully grow their email
list and then turn that into sales and
that's what our clients are seeing like
our client Ben he came in
$10,000 right away using exactly what
we're teaching in a brand new mentoring
program he'd gone through some different
training over the last couple years but
this was where he started to be able to
generate that kind of profit for himself
or like my client Ian Carrol he was able
to make over $40,000 a month in his
business and that's exactly what you
want to do every time that you have an
interaction with people you want to be
able to reiterate to them the value that
you offer how you work with people how
they can work with
you and that becomes a loop in their
mind when they're on your email list
you're you might be watching this right
now because you're on my email list or
you may join my email list after
watching this video and so with that
you're able to even if you're a
subscriber to my YouTube channel that's
almost as good as a as somebody on my
email list really to me if you're a
subscriber on my YouTube channel you're
going to see my content showing up on
your on your news feed when you go to
the for you page in uh YouTube these
videos pop up and and the algorithm
knows exactly what you need to hear and
so I would encourage you if you see my
videos popping up in the algorithm go
click on them go watch them those are
going to help you get more results in
your business okay and so growing your
email list that's one of the number one
thing that you got to do now you might
be thinking I don't know what to send to
people in an email you can use it AI
like Claude 35 to be able to send that
to people and write great emails you
might be saying oh gosh I don't know
what to use to grow my email list and so
again we can brainstorm with AI to be
able to come up with ideas for our
offers we are not alone in this process
there's a way to solve this to where we
don't need to struggle and wonder gosh
how can I grow my email list people
become your client because they trust
you but that
trust and really the commitment that
they make attach to that trust starts
waning I can trust somebody but if they
take too long and I'm not really bought
into wanting to take action with them I
will forget about taking action for
months and you do the same thing we all
do that same thing in our life and in
our business so our clients are going to
do that same thing and so realize that
that's what our job is is to actually
nurture that connection with people to
stay consistently in front of them and
remind them of the value that we offer
offer why we're here why we exist you're
in business to close sales you're in
business to get people results
simultaneously those two things can
exist and be true at the same time
you're in business to make money and
you're in business to provide results to
people and you want to have those on an
equal plane and you wanted that to be
very clear and obvious to everybody that
you're meeting it's very clear and
obvious I'm in business for you to
become a client of mine if you're a
coach if you're a mentor if you're a
trainer that's exactly what I want
because I can get you results
and that's what you can do with your
clients as well so listen I'd love to
work with you in my um wealthy coach
Academy program I keep almost saying
accelerator program because we just
renamed it that but the wealthy coach
Academy program it's incredible the
results that we're getting our clients
is amazing and so growing your email
list that's the thing we want to focus
on building a lead magnet that can grow
your email list something that you can
do and testing out what are people
responding to starting to grow in the
skill set of how do you deliver a
presentation to people once they sign up
on your email list what do you actually
have them sign up for generally it's
going be some kind of a piece of video
content and in that video content you
can make a presentation to people that
when you make that presentation it
actually gets them to buy into what
you're offering it persuades them to
purchase it this persuasive ability on
video is a skill that you can grow in I
have it I I impart it to my clients I
teach it to them I teach it to you in
our program
I didn't have it for years I actually
struggled so much with how to close
sales with how to get clients I was so
nervous to even talk about what I had
for sale and I was so like I wanted to
help so many people that I felt afraid
to let leave people out because they had
to pay money for what I offered and I
realized listen it's a form of service
to actually sell stuff to people that
provides value to them it's a form of
service to provide somebody with
something that's going to truly make
their life better and so that's what you
can do as well and I'd love to help you
do that all right stay plugged into our
Channel we'll talk soon have a good one
everybody